https://austinfilmfestival.com/site-map/privacy-policy/

Top Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footer
MenuAbout CloseAbout Close
Austin Film Festival furthers the art and craft of storytelling by inspiring and championing the work of writers, filmmakers, and all artists who use written and visual language to tell a story.
In addition to an 8 day film festival and 4 day Conference, we offer Year Round Events, a Young Filmmakers Program, a TV show,
Radio show, Podcast and more!
Austin Film Festival is really about creativity, about trying to help people find their voice. And it’s fun.”
- Ron Howard, 2009 Extraordinary Contribution to Filmmaking Award Recipient CloseStaff Close
The folks [at AFF] share our passion…Which is, of course, why they are so damn adept at crafting a conference that manages to satisfy the needs and desires of all of us attending.”
-Scott Rosenberg, screenwriter
Get to know the faces and stories of the people who run the show for the Austin Film Festival!
Want to work with us? We're always looking for folks to join our team whether it's through volunteering or interning or working with us on staff.
Check out our current opportunities below. Check out our job opportunities!Intern with us!Or volunteer! CloseBoardFAQsGet Involved CloseMembershipExclusive screenings, script readings, Conversations in Film, parties and more! MembershipCorporate MembershipDonateNot only is your donation tax deductible, but your support helps us to further the art and craft of filmmaking in our state.DonateInternWe're always looking for interns to join our team and be an integral part of pulling off our incredible programs!InternVolunteerVolunteers are a huge part of what we do at AFF. Plus, we have a ton of fun!Volunteer CloseSponsors and PartnersTestimonialsAccessibilityContact CloseNewsletterSubscribe to our newsletter to stay in touch!Sign up!PressFeel free to contact us with any press inquiries. Press Inquiries Close CloseWhat We Do CloseOn Story CloseWATCHThe weekly, 30-minute television series features interviews with today’s leading creators, writers and filmmakers. LISTENThe one-hour radio program & our podcast both feature the creative minds behind True Detective, The Graduate & more. READ Praised as recommended reading by film and media studies professors and filmmakers alike, the book offers introspections and recollections on the creative process. CloseFilm FestivalConferenceCompetitionsYoung Filmmakers Program CloseAFF’s Young Filmmakers Program introduces the arts of screenwriting and filmmaking to young people, ages 9-18, and provides them with venues for developing their storytelling talents. Here are a few of our programs:Camps & ClassesCheck out our workshops that help kids and young adults create their very own fabulous short films!2021 Summer Camps and ClassesDigital StorytellingOur program works with schools to improve communication skills through film.Digital StorytellingFestival ScholarshipsAustin Film Festival’s Young Filmmakers Scholarship Program grants access to over 300 scholarships for students and teachers in middle and high school.Festival and Conference Scholarship CloseStudent OpportunitiesYear-Round Events CloseCalendar of EventsWhether it's a networking event, workshop, conversation in film, or screening we've always got something coming up!Calendar of Events CloseSummer Camps & Classes CloseRegister Now! CloseMembership Program CloseBuy CloseHoliday BundlesWhat Should I Buy?Badges and Film Passes CloseWeekend BadgeConference BadgeProducers BadgeFilm & FoodStudent Conference BadgeGroup Conference BadgesGroup Producers BadgesFilm PassLone Star BadgeView all
CloseSummer Film Camp CloseSummer Camps & Classes CloseUpcoming Events CloseCalendar of EventsYear-round opportunities to attend conversations with industry pros, advance screenings, special retrospectives, filmmaker Q&As, and parties. CloseMembershipPartner With Us CloseSponsorshipAustin Film Festival welcomes new ideas and would love to work with any organization that shares interest in the arts and entertainment industry!DonateAustin Film Festival is a 501-3 organization. Your donation is tax-deductible to the extent allowed by the law. AFF has also made great strides promoting film production in Texas. Your support helps us to further the art and craft of filmmaking in our state. CloseShop more! CloseAdd-onsAttend our Awards Luncheon, Pitch in our Pitch Competition & party at our Film & Food Fundraising Gala!MerchandiseShirts! Posters! Books & more! Shop our incredible merchandise now! Close CloseFestival & Conference CloseRegister Now! Close
AFF offers a badge and pass options for everyone! Look through our different options, and find which badge is the perfect fit for you! What Badge is Right For Me?BADGE DISCOUNTS!
Students, members and entrants in our competitions all receive discounts on badges! Learn more.Learn About Our Discounts CloseFilm Festival CloseAustin Film Festival showcases an outstanding program of narrative, animation and documentary features and shorts, including premieres, advanced screenings, and independent films.
2020 FilmsBuy Now!Past Films CloseConference Close
My best experience ever at a film festival was in Austin.
So many festivals are flash over substance, a who’s who of movie stars.
Here, the creators are the stars. And rightly so. So if you want to write, direct or produce motion pictures and get paid for it, attend this festival.” – David McKenna (BLOW, AMERICAN HISTORY X)The ConferenceOur Conference is a one-of-a-kind event. About the ConferencePanelistsWe're pleased to bring the industry's best to Austin for you!PanelistsConference Tracks CloseAwards and Winners CloseFestival AwardsCheck out all our award categories! From jury awards to audience awards, AFF hands out over 40 awards each year!
CloseTestimonials CloseRead what others are saying about Austin Film Festival.
Close CloseCompetitions CloseScreenplay and Teleplay Submissions CloseCoverage AFF’s Coverage Program provides a detailed, constructive evaluation of your script and at $100 for feature scripts and $80 for teleplays, it’s the best bang for your buck!Coverage ProgramScript NotesAll of AFF’s readers are required to provide detailed, constructive notes for each script they review. We will provide reader comments to ALL entrants. For FREE!
Learn MoreLaunch Career
I’ve gotten meetings with production companies with first look deals at networks that I never would have gotten on my own."
Shelli Wright, 2015 Finalist Submit Now! CloseFilm Competition CloseWriters FestivalOur film competition recognizes the importance of narrative at the core of filmmaking.
Win BigThe Jury Award winners of our Narrative, Documentary and Animated Short categories officially qualify for an Academy Award®.Top 50 FestivalMoviemaker Magazine named AFF as one
of the “50 Film Festivals Worth the Entry Fee” in 2015-2019 and a “Top 25 Coolest Film Festivals in the World” in 2014.Submit Now! CloseDigital Series Competition CloseThis competition accepts both filmed and written submissions in an effort to find talented voices who can adapt their vision to emerging digital platforms.
AFF will select one winner who displays the strongest voice and greatest potential for establishing a digital series. ClosePlaywriting Competition ClosePlaywriting CompetitionAs Austin Film Festival continues to grow and expand, our vision also widens with the addition of new avenues for storytellers. The Playwriting Competition is open to full-length stage plays and gives playwrights a chance to explore our film and television conference. It will also allow film professionals to discover storytellers who have mastered the art and craft of stage drama. CloseFiction Podcast Script Competition CloseFiction Podcast Script CompetitionThe Fiction Podcast Script Competition, leverages our legacy of championing storytelling to launch writers into the emerging world of podcasts.
This competition connects audiences with incredible new stories, as well as connects writers with a medium that offers an incredible access to audiences and limitless opportunities to launch new stories. CloseYoung Filmmakers Competition CloseAFF’s Young Filmmakers Program introduces the arts of screenwriting and filmmaking to young people, ages 9-18, and provides them with venues for developing their storytelling talents. The program offers kids opportunities to share their creative work with peers, the public, and professional filmmakers and screenwriters. By introducing young people to the film industry, the program hopes to provide them new mediums to express their creativity, improve their communication skills, and benefit the entire arts community. Close CloseNews & Events CloseCalendar of EventsWe have events all year-round!
Whether it's an advance screening, a conversations with a filmmaker, or a screening from one of our series of film programs, we are thrilled to offer incredible year-round programming!
View calendar now!Buy Tickets for EventsAnnouncementsAFF 2020 Winners AnnouncedAFF 2020 Opening, Centerpiece, and Closing Night Films AnnouncementAFF 2020 Full Slate AnnouncementView all AFF BlogUpcoming EventsPress ReleasesRead our Press Releases and find out what we're up to! CloseDonate Now!CartON STORY
Austin Film Festival Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Austin Film Festival uses and protects any information that you give Austin Film Festival when you use this website.
Austin Film Festival is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Austin Film Festival may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 5/23/2018.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address, phone number, address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
The only cookies in use on our site are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it.
Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.
Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this Google page.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@austinfilmfestival.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union and the European Economic Area. It also addresses the export of personal data outside the EU and EEA. The GDPR aims primarily to give control to citizens and residents over their personal data and to simplify the regulatory environment for international business by unifying the regulation within the EU. Essentially, we’re giving you control of your data. If you’d like to read more you can visit the GDPR website here.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Primary SidebarRecent News
For inquiries, contact Kelly Lafargue marketing@austinfilmfestival.com o 512.478.4795   FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE Austin, TX - May 18, 2020 - Austin Film Festival & Writers Conference (AFF), the premier film festival recognizing the writers’ contributions to...  Read MoreWe're excited for our Festival & Conference in October, but if this season has made us aware of anything - it’s that we don’t want to wait. Launching this Wednesday, we’ve created a virtual experience...  Read MoreEven though the 27th Annual Writers Conference has ended, the friendships found, stories shared, and lessons learned will stick with us for a long time to come. Since we are a Writer’s Festival, it only...  Read MoreFilm: Jury Winners Film: Jury Honorable Mention Film: Audience Awards Screenplay & Teleplay 2020 Festival Awards Screenplay & Teleplay Competition Winners Screenplay & Teleplay Competition Winners Drama Feature Screenplay Award Presented by Writers Guild of...  Read More
Recent Posts
What I learned at AFF27
11/11/2020
2020 Winners
11/03/2020
2020’S BEST OF THE FEST
11/03/2020
AFF 2020 Winners Announced
11/02/2020
Staff Pick: Death of a Telemarketer
10/24/2020
FooterSearch site...
Sign Up For Our Newsletter
EmailFirst Name
©2020 Austin Film Festival • Austin Film Festival is a Not for Profit 501(c)(3) Corporation. Site by:BeiBay• Custom icons & base colors by Mosak.Sponsors.Privacy Policy.Store & Refund Policy.AFF Policies.Contact.Sitemap.On Story
Privacy Preferences
I Agree
